Register of the Gerald Lee Warren papers, 1956-1994
Hoover Institution Archives
- White House Office File, 1969-1977 (Boxes 27-89)
  - Travel
    - Foreign
      - Trips
        - 1974
          - Martinique, December 14-16
            - Communiques (Box-folder 89: 29)
            - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 89: 30)
            - Pool reports (Box-folder 89: 31)
            - Press conferences (Box-folder 89: 32)
            - Press releases (Box-folder 89: 33)
            - Remarks (Box-folder 89: 34)
            - Schedules (Box-folder 89: 35)
        - 1975
          - Europe, May 29-June 4
            - Pool reports (Box-folder 89: 36)
            - Press conferences (Box-folder 89: 37)
            - Press releases (Box-folder 89: 38)
            - Remarks (Box-folder 89: 39)
            - Schedules (Box-folder 89: 40)
            - Statements (Box-folder 89: 41)
            - Telegrams (Box-folder 89: 42)
            - Television news reports (Box-folder 89: 43)
          - Soviet Union (U.S. delegates), news summaries, July 5 (Box-folder 89: 44)
          - Europe, July 26-29
            - Press conferences (Box-folder 89: 45)
            - Remarks (Box-folder 89: 46)
            - Statements (Box-folder 89: 47)
            - Television news reports (Box-folder 89: 48)
          - Yugoslavia, press conferences, August 4 (Box-folder 89: 49)
  - Wire releases
    - Undated (Box-folder 89: 50)
    - 1974 July (Box-folder 89: 51)
- White House Subject File, 1969-1977 (Boxes 90-217)
  Brochures, correspondence, executive orders, interviews, meetings, memoranda, messages, newsletters, news summaries, pool reports, press briefings, press conferences, press releases, printed matter, proclamations, remarks, schedules, statements, telegrams, and television news reports relating to the cabinet, Congress, guidelines for declassifying government papers, domestic programs, United States relations with foreign nations, issues involving foreign aid and foreign trade, American prisoners of war and Americans missing in action, interaction between the White House and the media, the Republican party and the elections, state of the union messages, the plans of reorganizing the administrative structure of the White House and the federal government, presidential appointees and the rules of conduct for the White House staff, President Nixon's inauguration, his health, and the controversy surrounding the Watergate break-in, arranged alphabetically by physical form.
  - Cabinet
    - General (Box-folder 90: 1)
    - Meetings
      - Undated (Box-folder 90: 2)
      - 1969
        - April (Box-folder 90: 3)
        - August-September (Box-folder 90: 4)
          Holograph notes.
      - 1970 November (Box-folder 90: 5)
      - 1971
        - February-May (Box-folder 90: 6-9)
        - November (Box-folder 90: 10)
      - 1972 June-August (Box-folder 90: 11-13)
      - 1973
        - January-February (Box-folder 90: 14-15)
        - April (Box-folder 90: 16)
        - June (Box-folder 90: 17)
        - October (Box-folder 90: 18)
        - December (Box-folder 90: 19)
      - 1974
        - January-March (Box-folder 90: 20-22)
        - May-September (Box-folder 90: 23-27)
      - 1975 April-May (Box-folder 90: 28-29)
    - Memoranda
      - 1970 February (Box-folder 90: 30)
      - 1972 January (Box-folder 90: 31)
    - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 90: 32)
    - Press briefings
      - 1971 August (Box-folder 90: 33)
      - 1974 September (Box-folder 90: 34)
    - Press releases, 1972 June (Box-folder 90: 35)
    - Remarks
      - Undated (Box-folder 90: 36)
      - 1970 December (Box-folder 90: 37)
      - 1972
        - January (Box-folder 90: 38)
        - December (Box-folder 90: 39)
    - Schedules, 1970 August (Box-folder 90: 40)
  - Congress
    - Brochures, undated (Box-folder 90: 41)
    - Correspondence
      - Undated (Box-folder 90: 42)
      - 1964 June (Box-folder 90: 43)
      - 1966
        - March (Box-folder 90: 44)
        - October (Box-folder 90: 45)
      - 1969 November-December (Box-folder 90: 46-47)
      - 1970
        - March-August (Box-folder 90: 48-53)
        - November-December (Box-folder 90: 54-55)
      - 1971
        - January-August (Box-folder 90: 56-63)
        - September-December (Box-folder 91: 1-4)
      - 1972
        - January (Box-folder 91: 5)
        - March-September (Box-folder 91: 6-12)
        - November (Box-folder 91: 13)
      - 1973
        - January-September (Box-folder 91: 14-22)
        - November-December (Box-folder 91: 23-24)
      - 1974
        - January-August (Box-folder 91: 25-32)
        - October-November (Box-folder 91: 33-34)
      - 1975 February-July (Box-folder 91: 35-40)
    - Directory, 1973 January (Box-folder 91: 41)
    - Fact sheets
      - Undated (Box-folder 91: 42)
      - 1956 (Box-folder 92: 1)
      - 1964 August (Box-folder 92: 2)
      - 1967 July (Box-folder 92: 3)
      - 1969
        - June (Box-folder 92: 4)
        - December (Box-folder 92: 5)
      - 1970
        - General (Box-folder 92: 6)
        - May-June (Box-folder 92: 7-8)
        - December (Box-folder 92: 9)
      - 1971
        - General (Box-folder 92: 10)
        - January (Box-folder 92: 11)
        - October-December (Box-folder 92: 12-14)
      - 1972
        - General (Box-folder 92: 15)
        - January (Box-folder 92: 16)
        - March (Box-folder 92: 17)
        - June-August (Box-folder 92: 18-20)
        - October (Box-folder 92: 21)
      - 1973
        - General (Box-folder 92: 22)
        - January-March (Box-folder 92: 23-25)
        - September (Box-folder 92: 26)
        - December (Box-folder 92: 27)
      - 1974
        - General (Box-folder 92: 28)
        - January-February (Box-folder 92: 29-30)
        - April-August (Box-folder 92: 31-34)
        - November-December (Box-folder 92: 35-36)
      - 1975
        - April-July (Box-folder 92: 37-40)
        - December (Box-folder 92: 41)
      - 1977 March (Box-folder 92: 42)
    - General (Box-folder 92: 43)
    - Hearings
      - General, 1974 (Box-folder 92: 44)
      - 1975 June (Box-folder 92: 45)
    - Interviews
      - Undated (Box-folder 93: 1)
      - 1973
        - February (Box-folder 93: 2)
        - April (Box-folder 93: 3)
        - September-November (Box-folder 93: 4-6)
      - 1974
        - January (Box-folder 93: 7)
        - March-April (Box-folder 93: 8-9)
        - July-August (Box-folder 93: 10-11)
      - 1975
        - April (Box-folder 93: 12)
        - May-June (Box-folder 93: 13-14)
    - Meetings
      - Undated (Box-folder 93: 15)
      - 1969
        - May (Box-folder 93: 16)
        - July (Box-folder 93: 17)
        - December (Box-folder 93: 18)
      - 1970
        - March-May (Box-folder 93: 19-21)
        - July-August (Box-folder 93: 22-23)
        - October-December (Box-folder 93: 24-26)
      - 1971 January-November (Box-folder 93: 27-37)
      - 1972
        - January-February (Box-folder 93: 38-39)
        - March (Box-folder 94: 1)
        - May-June (Box-folder 94: 2-3)
        - September-October (Box-folder 94: 4-5)
      - 1973
        - January-July (Box-folder 94: 6-12)
        - September-November (Box-folder 94: 13-15)
      - 1974 (Box-folder 94: 16-27)
      - 1975 January-June (Box-folder 94: 28-33)
    - Memoranda
      - Undated (Box-folder 94: 34)
      - 1969
        - March (Box-folder 94: 35)
        - November-December (Box-folder 94: 36-37)
      - 1970
        - February-March (Box-folder 94: 38-39)
        - May (Box-folder 94: 40)
        - July-August (Box-folder 94: 41-42)
        - October-December (Box-folder 94: 43-45)
      - 1971
        - January-February (Box-folder 95: 1-2)
        - April-December (Box-folder 95: 3-11)
      - 1972 January-October (Box-folder 95: 12-21)
      - 1973
        - January-April (Box-folder 95: 22-25)
        - June-August (Box-folder 95: 26-28)
        - September-December (Box-folder 96: 1-4)
      - 1974
        - January-February (Box-folder 96: 5-6)
        - April-May (Box-folder 96: 7-8)
        - July-August (Box-folder 96: 9-10)
        - October-November (Box-folder 96: 11-12)
      - 1975 February (Box-folder 96: 13)
    - Messages
      - Undated (Box-folder 96: 14)
      - 1969 February (Box-folder 96: 15)
      - 1970
        - January-February (Box-folder 96: 16-17)
        - May-June (Box-folder 96: 18-19)
        - August-October (Box-folder 96: 20-22)
        - December (Box-folder 96: 23)
      - 1971
        - January-April (Box-folder 96: 24-27)
        - June-September (Box-folder 96: 28-31)
        - November-December (Box-folder 96: 32-33)
      - 1972
        - February (Box-folder 96: 34)
        - April-October (Box-folder 96: 35-41)
        - December (Box-folder 96: 42)
      - 1973
        - January-July (Box-folder 96: 43-49)
        - September-October (Box-folder 96: 50-51)
      - 1974
        - February-May (Box-folder 96: 52-55)
        - July-November (Box-folder 96: 56-60)
      - 1975
        - March (Box-folder 96: 61)
        - May-July (Box-folder 96: 62-64)
      - 1977 March (Box-folder 96: 65)
    - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 96: 66)
    - Newsletters, 1975 June (Box-folder 97: 1)
    - News summaries
      - Undated (Box-folder 97: 2)
      - 1970 December (Box-folder 97: 3)
      - 1971 September (Box-folder 97: 4)
      - 1974 November (Box-folder 97: 5)
      - 1975
        - July (Box-folder 97: 6)
        - September (Box-folder 97: 7)
    - Pool reports, 1974 May (Box-folder 97: 8)
    - Press briefings
      - Undated (Box-folder 97: 9)
      - 1969 November (Box-folder 97: 10)
      - 1970
        - April (Box-folder 97: 11)
        - June-July (Box-folder 97: 12-13)
        - September (Box-folder 97: 14)
        - November (Box-folder 97: 15)
      - 1971
        - January (Box-folder 97: 16)
        - April (Box-folder 97: 17)
        - June-October (Box-folder 97: 18-22)
      - 1972 April-October (Box-folder 97: 23-29)
      - 1973
        - February (Box-folder 97: 30)
        - April (Box-folder 97: 31)
        - June (Box-folder 97: 32)
        - July-December (Box-folder 97: 33-38)
      - 1974 February-December (Box-folder 97: 39-49)
      - 1975 January-July (Box-folder 97: 50-56)
    - Press conferences
      - Undated (Box-folder 97: 57)
      - 1969 September (Box-folder 97: 58)
      - 1970
        - March-May (Box-folder 97: 59-61)
        - June-September (Box-folder 98: 1-4)
        - November-December (Box-folder 98: 5-6)
      - 1971
        - January-September (Box-folder 98: 7-15)
        - November-December (Box-folder 98: 16-17)
      - 1972
        - January-October (Box-folder 98: 18-27)
        - December (Box-folder 98: 28)
      - 1973
        - February-March (Box-folder 98: 29-30)
        - May (Box-folder 98: 31)
        - July (Box-folder 98: 32)
        - September (Box-folder 98: 33)
        - December (Box-folder 98: 34)
      - 1974
        - January-May (Box-folder 98: 35-39)
        - August (Box-folder 98: 40)
      - 1975
        - March (Box-folder 98: 41)
        - May-June (Box-folder 98: 42-43)
    - Press releases
      - Undated (Box-folder 99: 1)
      - General (Box-folder 99: 2)
      - 1969 December (Box-folder 99: 3)
      - 1970
        - March (Box-folder 99: 4)
        - June-July (Box-folder 99: 5-6)
        - October-December (Box-folder 99: 7-9)
      - 1971
        - General (Box-folder 99: 10)
        - January-February (Box-folder 99: 11-12)
        - April-May (Box-folder 99: 13-14)
        - September-December (Box-folder 99: 15-18)
      - 1972
        - General (Box-folder 99: 19)
        - March (Box-folder 99: 20)
        - May-October (Box-folder 99: 21-26)
        - December (Box-folder 99: 27)
      - 1973
        - February-June (Box-folder 99: 28-32)
        - August (Box-folder 99: 33)
        - November-December (Box-folder 99: 34-35)
      - 1974 January-September (Box-folder 99: 36-44)
      - 1975 March-July (Box-folder 99: 45-49)
    - Printed matter
      - 1973 October (Box-folder 100: 1)
      - 1975
        - January (Box-folder 100: 2)
        - April (Box-folder 100: 3)
    - Proclamations, 1970 October (Box-folder 100: 4)
    - Remarks
      - Undated (Box-folder 100: 5)
      - 1970
        - January (Box-folder 100: 6)
        - March (Box-folder 100: 7)
        - May (Box-folder 100: 8)
        - August (Box-folder 100: 9)
        - December (Box-folder 100: 10)
      - 1971
        - General (Box-folder 100: 11)
        - January-February (Box-folder 100: 12-13)
        - April (Box-folder 100: 14)
        - June-July (Box-folder 100: 15-16)
        - September-October (Box-folder 100: 17-18)
      - 1972 February (Box-folder 100: 19)
      - 1973
        - January-May (Box-folder 100: 20-24)
        - September-October (Box-folder 100: 25-26)
      - 1974
        - March (Box-folder 100: 27)
        - May (Box-folder 100: 28)
        - July (Box-folder 100: 29)
        - September (Box-folder 100: 30)
        - October (Box-folder 100: 31)
      - 1975 February-July (Box-folder 100: 32-37)
    - Reports
      - 1971 (Box-folder 100: 38)
      - 1972 August (Box-folder 100: 39)
      - 1975 August (Box-folder 100: 40)
    - Schedules
      - Undated (Box-folder 100: 41)
      - 1970 November-December (Box-folder 100: 42-43)
      - 1971
        - January-February (Box-folder 100: 44-45)
        - April-July (Box-folder 100: 46-49)
        - September (Box-folder 100: 50)
      - 1972
        - April (Box-folder 100: 51)
        - June-August (Box-folder 100: 52-54)
        - October (Box-folder 100: 55)
      - 1973
        - January-February (Box-folder 100: 56-57)
        - April-May (Box-folder 100: 58-59)
      - 1974
        - May (Box-folder 100: 60)
        - August (Box-folder 100: 61)
        - September (Box-folder 100: 62)
    - Statements
      - Undated (Box-folder 101: 1)
      - 1969 November-December (Box-folder 101: 2-3)
      - 1970
        - March-October (Box-folder 101: 4-11)
        - December (Box-folder 101: 12)
      - 1971
        - January (Box-folder 101: 13)
        - March (Box-folder 101: 14)
        - May (Box-folder 101: 15)
        - August-December (Box-folder 101: 16-20)
      - 1972
        - January (Box-folder 101: 21)
        - March (Box-folder 101: 22)
        - May (Box-folder 101: 23)
        - July-August (Box-folder 101: 24-25)
        - October-December (Box-folder 101: 26-28)
      - 1973
        - April (Box-folder 101: 29)
        - June-December (Box-folder 101: 30-36)
      - 1974
        - March-October (Box-folder 101: 37-44)
        - December (Box-folder 101: 45)
      - 1975
        - February (Box-folder 101: 46)
        - May-July (Box-folder 101: 47-49)
        - December (Box-folder 101: 50)
    - Telegrams
      - Undated (Box-folder 101: 51)
      - 1970 August (Box-folder 101: 52)
    - Television news reports
      - Undated (Box-folder 101: 53)
      - 1971
        - September (Box-folder 101: 54)
        - November (Box-folder 101: 55)
        - December (Box-folder 101: 56)
      - 1972
        - January (Box-folder 101: 57)
        - October (Box-folder 101: 58)
        - December (Box-folder 101: 59)
      - 1973 January (Box-folder 101: 60)
      - 1974
        - April (Box-folder 101: 61)
        - July (Box-folder 101: 62)
    - Testimonies
      - 1971 June (Box-folder 101: 63)
      - 1975 January (Box-folder 101: 64)
    - Wire releases, 1971 January (Box-folder 101: 65)
  - Declassification
    - Correspondence, 1972 April (Box-folder 102: 1)
    - Executive orders
      - 1972 March (Box-folder 102: 2)
      - 1975 June (Box-folder 102: 3)
    - Fact sheets, 1972
      - May (Box-folder 102: 4)
      - August (Box-folder 102: 5)
    - General (Box-folder 102: 6)
    - Meetings, 1971 July (Box-folder 102: 7)
    - Memoranda
      - 1971 June (Box-folder 102: 8)
      - 1972
        - May (Box-folder 102: 9)
        - November (Box-folder 102: 10)
    - Messages, 1974 October (Box-folder 102: 11)
    - News summaries, 1971 June-July (Box-folder 102: 12-13)
    - Press briefings, 1972 May (Box-folder 102: 14)
    - Press conferences
      - 1971
        - June (Box-folder 102: 15)
        - August (Box-folder 102: 16)
      - 1972 March (Box-folder 102: 17)
    - Press releases, 1972 August (Box-folder 102: 18)
    - Reports, 1974 April (Box-folder 102: 19)
    - Statements
      - Undated (Box-folder 102: 20)
      - 1972
        - March (Box-folder 102: 21)
        - May (Box-folder 102: 22)
      - 1974 May (Box-folder 102: 23)
    - Television news reports
      - 1971 June (Box-folder 102: 24)
      - 1974 November (Box-folder 102: 25)
  - Domestic programs
    - Correspondence, 1970 July (Box-folder 102: 26)
    - Fact sheets
      - Undated (Box-folder 102: 27)
      - 1970 June (Box-folder 102: 28)
    - Interviews
      - 1971 January (Box-folder 102: 29)
      - 1973 October (Box-folder 102: 30)
      - 1974 October (Box-folder 102: 31)
    - Meetings
      - 1970 August (Box-folder 102: 32)
      - 1971 May-July (Box-folder 102: 33-35)
      - 1972 January (Box-folder 102: 36)
      - 1973 August (Box-folder 102: 37)
      - 1974
        - May (Box-folder 102: 38)
        - July-August (Box-folder 102: 39-40)
      - 1975 March-June (Box-folder 102: 41-44)
    - Memoranda
      - 1969 October (Box-folder 102: 45)
      - 1971
        - June (Box-folder 102: 46)
        - September (Box-folder 102: 47)
      - 1972
        - January (Box-folder 102: 48)
        - July (Box-folder 103: 1)
      - 1973 August (Box-folder 103: 2)
      - 1974
        - February (Box-folder 103: 3)
        - July (Box-folder 103: 4)
    - Messages
      - 1970 March (Box-folder 103: 5)
      - 1971 February (Box-folder 103: 6)
      - 1973 February (Box-folder 103: 7)
      - 1974 September (Box-folder 103: 8)
    - News summaries
      - Undated (Box-folder 103: 9)
      - 1974 September-October (Box-folder 103: 10-11)
      - 1975 February (Box-folder 103: 12)
    - Press briefings
      - Undated (Box-folder 103: 13)
      - 1969 October (Box-folder 103: 14)
      - 1970
        - June (Box-folder 103: 15)
        - September (Box-folder 103: 16)
        - December (Box-folder 103: 17)
      - 1971
        - June (Box-folder 103: 18)
        - September-December (Box-folder 103: 19-22)
      - 1972
        - January-February (Box-folder 103: 23-24)
        - August-December (Box-folder 103: 25-29)
      - 1973 February (Box-folder 103: 30)
      - 1974
        - March-April (Box-folder 103: 31-32)
        - August (Box-folder 103: 33)
        - October (Box-folder 103: 34)
      - 1975
        - January (Box-folder 103: 35)
        - May (Box-folder 103: 36)
    - Press conferences
      - 1970
        - March-July (Box-folder 103: 37-41)
        - November-December (Box-folder 103: 42-43)
      - 1971
        - January-March (Box-folder 103: 44-46)
        - April-June (Box-folder 104: 1-3)
        - August-December (Box-folder 104: 4-8)
      - 1972 March-November (Box-folder 104: 9-17)
      - 1973
        - January-June (Box-folder 104: 18-23)
        - September-November (Box-folder 105: 1-3)
      - 1974
        - January-March (Box-folder 105: 4-6)
        - May-July (Box-folder 105: 7-9)
        - October-December (Box-folder 105: 10-12)
      - 1975
        - January-February (Box-folder 105: 13-14)
        - June (Box-folder 105: 15)
    - Press releases
      - 1970 April (Box-folder 105: 16)
      - 1973 September (Box-folder 105: 17)
    - Printed matter, 1971 October (Box-folder 105: 18)
    - Remarks
      - Undated (Box-folder 105: 19)
      - 1969 December (Box-folder 105: 20)
      - 1973
        - April (Box-folder 105: 21)
        - August (Box-folder 105: 22)
      - 1974 May (Box-folder 105: 23)
    - Schedules, 1974 June (Box-folder 105: 24)
    - Statements
      - Undated (Box-folder 105: 25)
      - 1969 July (Box-folder 105: 26)
      - 1972
        - October (Box-folder 105: 27)
        - December (Box-folder 105: 28)
      - 1973
        - January (Box-folder 105: 29)
        - October (Box-folder 105: 30)
      - 1975 March (Box-folder 105: 31)
    - Television news reports
      - 1973 November (Box-folder 105: 32)
      - 1974 February-April (Box-folder 105: 33-35)
    - Wire releases
      - Undated (Box-folder 105: 36)
      - 1974 July (Box-folder 105: 37)
    - Agriculture
      - Correspondence
        - 1970 February (Box-folder 106: 1)
        - 1972 June (Box-folder 106: 2)
        - 1973
          - July-August (Box-folder 106: 3-4)
          - October (Box-folder 106: 5)
      - Executive orders
        - 1974 March (Box-folder 106: 6)
        - 1975 April (Box-folder 106: 7)
      - Fact sheets
        - Undated (Box-folder 106: 8)
        - 1971 April-May (Box-folder 106: 9-10)
        - 1972 June (Box-folder 106: 11)
        - 1973
          - March (Box-folder 106: 12)
          - August (Box-folder 106: 13)
      - Meetings
        - 1970 December (Box-folder 106: 14)
        - 1971 April-May (Box-folder 106: 15-16)
        - 1973 February (Box-folder 106: 17)
        - 1974
          - March (Box-folder 106: 18)
          - June-August (Box-folder 106: 19-21)
          - October (Box-folder 106: 22)
      - Memoranda
        - 1970 December (Box-folder 106: 23)
        - 1971
          - April (Box-folder 106: 24)
          - July (Box-folder 106: 25)
          - November (Box-folder 106: 26)
        - 1972 June (Box-folder 106: 27)
        - 1974
          - March (Box-folder 106: 28)
          - August (Box-folder 106: 29)
      - Messages
        - 1970 June (Box-folder 106: 30)
        - 1971 June (Box-folder 106: 31)
        - 1973 July (Box-folder 106: 32)
        - 1974 September (Box-folder 106: 33)
        - 1975 June (Box-folder 106: 34)
      - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 106: 35)
      - News summaries, 1974 November (Box-folder 106: 36)
      - Press briefings
        - 1971
          - March (Box-folder 106: 37)
          - May-July (Box-folder 106: 38-40)
        - 1972 October (Box-folder 106: 41)
        - 1974
          - February-March (Box-folder 106: 42-43)
          - October (Box-folder 106: 44)
          - December (Box-folder 106: 45)
      - Press conferences
        - 1970 October (Box-folder 106: 46)
        - 1973
          - April (Box-folder 106: 47)
          - August (Box-folder 106: 48)
        - 1975 May (Box-folder 106: 49)
      - Press releases
        - 1973 March (Box-folder 106: 50)
        - 1974 July (Box-folder 106: 51)
      - Proclamations
        - 1970
          - March (Box-folder 106: 52)
          - October (Box-folder 106: 53)
          - December (Box-folder 106: 54)
        - 1971
          - April (Box-folder 106: 55)
          - November (Box-folder 106: 56)
        - 1972
          - March (Box-folder 106: 57)
          - November-December (Box-folder 106: 58-59)
        - 1973
          - March-May (Box-folder 106: 60-62)
          - July (Box-folder 106: 63)
          - November (Box-folder 106: 64)
        - 1974
          - January-March (Box-folder 106: 65-67)
          - June (Box-folder 106: 68)
      - Remarks
        - 1970 December (Box-folder 106: 69)
        - 1971
          - April-May (Box-folder 106: 70-71)
          - December (Box-folder 106: 72)
        - 1972
          - July (Box-folder 106: 73)
          - October (Box-folder 106: 74)
        - 1974 March (Box-folder 106: 75)
        - 1975 May-June (Box-folder 106: 76-77)
      - Reports
        - 1970 February (Box-folder 107: 1)
        - 1974 November (Box-folder 107: 2)
      - Schedules, 1971 April-May (Box-folder 107: 3-4)
      - Statements
        - 1970 November (Box-folder 107: 5)
        - 1972
          - June (Box-folder 107: 6)
            Includes draft.
          - October (Box-folder 107: 7)
          - December (Box-folder 107: 8)
        - 1973 August (Box-folder 107: 9)
      - Telegrams, 1974 March (Box-folder 107: 10)